foreign
so today I will talk about the
background or the introduction about
Prudential company so do you guys know
what is Prudential company Prudential
Assurance Malaysia p a m b are also
known as Prudential so this company is a
leading and Innovative insurance company
in Malaysia this company serves the
savings protection and investment needs
of Malaysia offer a full range of
Financial Solutions through its branches
and agency Forest so Prudential was
established purposely to help people to
get the most out of Life by making
Healthcare being affordable and
accessible Prudential has provided two
type of insurance which are life
insurance and also medical insurance
so medical insurance is an insurance
that will protect a person from the need
that to pay a high medical cost this is
because medical costs will cover all the
treatments including the consultation
treatment costs and other expenses that
can certainly being add up to a health
design so medical and health insurance
policies are to help the insurance cover
some of all the health care that might
arise in exchange for a premium if you
want to get no better about Prudential
company you need to watch this video
till the end let us move to the next
next
Prudential in this insurance company
called oriental insurance that is health
insurance health insurance has been
divided into two parts namely medical
plant and critical Idols lab the basic
medical plan has been known as Pro my
medical class is a customer stable
solution through portrait from medical
emergency and Rising high enough costs
consultation treatment cause and other
expenses can
a large amount not to mention High care
costs may increase due to Medical
inflation
through my medical class office a choice
of plans to meet your unique medical
coverage needs an affordability
you can choose from True Value men and
promise depending on the premium and
lifetime limit you're required the
second part of medical insurance is
critical ionose plan
this critical understanding policy has
been known as through my critical term
it's covered that brings you a long time
to spend as much as you want if you have
a critical ideas
because critical illness reflects your
Finance in ways you don't expect
in addition to long journey recovery UV
has to consider other expenses beside
medical costs such as the loss of Japan
daily universes adaptation to your home
and more this is why investing in
critical earnings Insurance can save
your from Financial absorption then
such as cancer
surgery
control
and kidney failure
my name is
developing of her insurance in
production insurance
they have five benefit in health
insurance first extensive coverage
Financial Protection health and wellness
programs access to a vast network of
provider and lastly is peace of mind
expensive coverage Prudential Health
insurance policy offers comprehensive
medical coverage including
hospitalization surgeries and diagnostic
tests the policies are designed to meet
the varying Health Care needs of
individuals and their families the
second benefit is financial protection
with a Prudential Health insurance
policies policyholders are protected
from unforeseen medical expenses to the
insurance provider pays a significant
portion of medical business which can be
substation depending on severity of the
illness or injury
next health and wellness program
Prudential of first health and wellness
program that include health screening
preventive care and wellness discount
these programs help individuals stay
healthy and prevent Future Health Care
issues number four is access to a vast
network of providers Prudential has an
extensive networks or providers
including hospitals clinics and doctors
this ensure policy products have access
to Quality Healthcare service when they
need it
is peace of mind Venture health
insurance policies provide policy orders
with Financial Security knowing that
they are protected from The High Cost of
medical care this piece of mind is
invaluable especially during times of
illness or injury I will continue to
present about the exclusion of the
policy exclusion for Prudential Health
Insurance Malaysia varies but based on
the specific policy and can chosen
however common exclusion in health
insurance coverage typically include
pre-existing conditions expenses related
to pre-assisted medical condition may be
as good for a certain waiting period
after purchasing the policy plisty means
a physical or mental condition that
exists before submission of The Proposal
form it won't be covered if the
condition wasn't disclosed when the
proposal form was submit or the policy
was reinstate the non-disclosure may
also cause the body system and benefit
the change the second exclusion is
qualifying or waiting period during the
waiting period your insurer will not
allow you to make any claim for medical
condition usually 30 days from when you
first buy the cover the third exclusion
is cosmetic procedure health insurance
does not cover cosmetic procedure to
improve appearance unless it is
medically necessary treatment or surgery
performed for cosmetic reasons such as
plastic surgery are not covered other
exclusion for health insurance policy is
staff and Fleet injuries
injury resulting from self-harm or
attempts research are generally exclude
net certain high-risk activity injury or
illness resulting from participating in
certain high-risk activity such as
extreme sport or dangerous hobby may be
not recovered
and lastly fertility treatment fertility
treatments such as in vitro
fertilization can cause thousands of
Ringgit unfortunately health insurance
does not cover fertility treatment
this exclusion may vary from policy to
policy so it is important to carefully
review at the term and condition of the
specific insurance plan offered by
potential Insurance Malaysia before
making the purchase
[Music]